myitreturn.com 2016-04-28

# Privacy Policy - Skorydov myITreturn

Your privacy is important to **Skorydov myITreturn**. This statement discloses the information practices for **Skorydov myITreturn** Web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. 

* * *

#### Personal information

In general, you can visit **Skorydov myITreturn** on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you. 

You may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information, such as your name and address or e-mail id, to correspond with you, to process an order, or to provide you with a subscription. You may give us your credit card details to buy something from us or a description of your education and work experience in connection with a job opening at **Skorydov myITreturn** that you wish to be considered for. We intend to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you; if you tell us that you do not want us to use this information to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes. If you give us personal information about somebody else, such as a spouse or work colleague, we will assume that you have their permission to do so. 

#### Using and Sharing Personal Information

he following paragraphs describe in more detail how **Skorydov myITreturn** may use your personal information and with whom we may share it. Depending on the type of **Skorydov myITreturn** Web site you are visiting, one or more of the paragraphs may apply. For example, if you order a product from an **Skorydov myITreturn** Web site, your information will be handled as described in such paragraphs as Fulfilling Your Transaction Request and Marketing Use. 

#### Fulfilling your transaction request

If you request something from an **Skorydov myITreturn** Web site, for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information, with others, for instance, other parts of **Skorydov myITreturn** , **Skorydov myITreturn** Associates, financial institutions, shipping companies, postal or government authorities (for example, Income tax authorities) involved in fulfillment. In connection with a transaction we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes. 

#### Marketing Use

The information you provide to **Skorydov myITreturn** on certain **Skorydov myITreturn** Web sites may also be used by **Skorydov myITreturn** and selected third parties for marketing purposes. Before we use it, however, we will offer you the opportunity to choose whether or not to have your information used in this way. You can opt out of such programs. 

#### **Skorydov myITreturn** Discussion Forums and Chat Rooms

If you participate in an **Skorydov myITreturn** discussion forum or chat room, you should be aware that the information you provide there will be made broadly available to others, potentially inside or outside **Skorydov myITreturn** , who have access to that discussion forum or chat room. Also, please recognize that individual forums and chat rooms may have additional rules and conditions. Each participant's opinion on a forum or chat room is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of **Skorydov myITreturn**. 

#### Other **Skorydov myITreturn** Web Site Notices

In some cases, specific **Skorydov myITreturn** Web sites may contain other notices about their use and the information practices applicable to those sites. 

#### Information Security and Quality 

We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. We implement appropriate measures and processes, such as using encryption when transmitting certain sensitive information, to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality. 

#### Supplementing Information

From time to time we may supplement information you give us via an **Skorydov myITreturn** Web site with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information about businesses. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide a better service. 

#### Supplementing Information

We sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to our Web sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit, and we also measure visitor activity on **Skorydov myITreturn** Web sites, but we do so in ways that keep the information non-identifiable. This information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." **Skorydov myITreturn** or others on **Skorydov myITreturn** 's behalf may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. 

Also, when we collect personal data from you in a transaction, we may extract some information about that transaction in an non-identifiable format and combine it with other non-identifiable information such as clickstream data. This information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. This information is not reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner you can disable your cookies. 

We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. Some **Skorydov myITreturn** pages use cookies, sent by **Skorydov myITreturn** or its third party vendors, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Web site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly. 

#### Service Quality Monitoring

Certain Web transactions may also involve you calling us or our calling you. Please be aware that it is **Skorydov myITreturn** 's general practice to monitor and in some cases record such calls for staff training or quality assurance purposes. 

#### Online Advertising

Certain companies help us deliver interactive on-line advertising such as banner ads. These companies may collect and use information about customers to help us better understand the offers, promotions, and types of advertising that are most appealing to our customers. 

#### Personalized URL Link

On occasion, we may personalize and customize Web sites for certain visitors. If you visit one of these sites, you may find it customized with references to products and/or services that we believe may be of interest to you, based on your previous interactions with **Skorydov myITreturn** and information you have provided to us. While you are visiting these Web sites, we may collect information about your visit to better tailor the site to your interests. An invitation to visit one of these Web sites is usually presented as a personalized URL in an e-mail, a notice on a Web site registration page, or as a response to you logging on to a certain Web site. 

If you choose to visit one of these Web sites, you are agreeing to let **Skorydov myITreturn** collect information about your visits and also to its association with other information about you and your relationship with **Skorydov myITreturn** . If you do not wish your information to be used in this way, do not accept the invitation to visit these sites. 

#### Disclosures Required By Law

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government orders 

#### Data Security and Backup

We store your data on online servers ensuring best possible protection from our end. We intend to protect it in encrypted format and also take back-up at defined intervals to ensure there is minimum data loss in case of any unfortunate server crash. To enhance your browsing experience, the data servers may be located at various places including places outside India. 

#### Links to non- **Skorydov myITreturn** Web sites

**Skorydov myITreturn** Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. **Skorydov myITreturn** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other Web sites. 

* * *
